var questionCount = 0;
    var Questions = {
        "quiz": [
            {
                "questionNumber": "",
                "question": "Which two games were originally sold with the NES system when it was released in 1985 ?",

                "choices": ["Super Mario Bros and Duck Hunt", "Gyromite and Duck Hutn", "Tetris and Mega Man"],

                "answer": "Gyromite and Duck Hutn",

                "comments": "When the NES first Hit the U.S, it came with 'Gyromite' and 'Duck Hunt'"
                },

            {
                "questionNumber": "",
                "question": "What mystical object is Link searching for in The Legend of Zelda ?",

                "choices": ["trefoil", "Truffle", "Triforce"],

                "answer": "Triforce",
                "comments": "Zelda broke the Triforce of Wisdom into many pieces then hid them all over Hyrule to keep them from Ganon. As you play the game, you must collect the pieces to reassemble the Triforce"
                },

            {
                "questionNumber": "",
                "question": "How many copies of the NES version of Super Mario Bros. did Nintendo sell? ?",

                "choices": ["40 Million", "400 Million", "4 Billion"],

                "answer": "40 Million",
                "comments": "Nintendo sold more than 40 million copies of Super Mario Bros., which came out in 1985 in Japan and hit U.S. shelves the next year."
            },

            {
                "questionNumber": "",
                "question": "Who is the big boss that Mario must defeat in the original Super Mario Bros. ?",

                "choices": ["Luigi", "Bowser", "Ganondorf", "Peach"],

                "answer": "Bowser",
                "comments": "Mario must defeat Bowser to beat the game and save Princess Toadstool and the entire Mushroom Kingdom.",

            },

            {
                "questionNumber": "",
                "question": "What are the mushroom-like enemies that try to keep Mario from his mission ?",

                "choices": ["Koopas", "Goombas", "Shy-Guy", "Tanooki"],

                "answer": "Goombas",
                "comments": "Goombas can be defeated with fireballs or a simple stomp on the head. They should not be confused with the decidedly turtle-like Koopas."


            },

            {
                "questionNumber": "",
                "question": "How many different playable characters are in Super Mario Bros. 2 ?",

                "choices": ["one", "Two", "Four", "99 problems"],

                "answer": "Four",
                "comments": "You can play as Mario, Luigi, Toad or Princess Toadstool in the second NES Mario incarnation."
            },

            {
                "questionNumber": "",
                "question": "What is the Princess' special talent in Super Mario Bros. 2 ?",

                "choices": ["She can float", "She can Swim really fast", "She can shrink or grow", "she runs like forrest gump"],

                "answer": "She can float",
                "comments": "Each playable character in the game has a special talent. For Princess Toadstool, it's the ability to float over enemies or obstacles."

            },

            {
                "questionNumber": "",
                "question": "What does the POW block do in Super Mario Bros. 2 ?",

                "choices": ["Turns the characters invisible", "Starts the level over", "Kill all visible enemies", "Send Trump back to hell"],

                "answer": "Kills all visible enemies",
                "comments": "Picking up and dropping the POW block destroys every enemy on the screen."
            },

            {
                "questionNumber": "",
                "question": "What year did Super Mario Bros. 3 come out on NES ?",

                "choices": ["1986", "1987", "1988", "Let me call DR Emmet Brown"],

                "answer": "1988",
                "comments": "The third Mario game for NES hit shelves in 1988 and went on to sell more than 17 million copies."
            },

            {
                "questionNumber": "",
                "question": "Where does the final stage of each of the first seven worlds take place in Super Mario Bros. 3 ?",

                "choices": ["In a castle", "In the water", "In an airship", "In Metropolis"],

                "answer": "In a airship",
                "comments": "In the first seven worlds, Mario must hop aboard an airship and defeat one of the Koopalings. In the final level, he takes on Bowser himself."
            }
    ]

    }